[{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Throughput?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Error_Rate?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Jitter?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Latency?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Interplay_Factors?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Bandwidth?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"bw","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Congession?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Computer_Networks?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"sec","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"scope","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"n1","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Security?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"availabilty","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"modi","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"confid","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"integ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"interrr","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"sec","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Scope?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"s1","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"s2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"s3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"s4","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"scope","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"NCP is a subClass from Session","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"ISO_Standard is a subClass from Session","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Application is a subClass from Session","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Media_Access_Control_Sublayer is a subClass from Data_Link","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Presentation is a subClass from Data_Link","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Transport is a subClass from Data_Link","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Fully_Connected is a subClass from Mesh","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Hybrid is a subClass from Mesh","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Dairy_Chairs is a subClass from Mesh","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Silicon_Photo_Diode is a subClass from Infrared","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Satellites is a subClass from Infrared","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Microwave is a subClass from Infrared","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SNTP is a subClass from NTP","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"NetBIOS is a subClass from NTP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP is a subClass from NTP","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Negative_Filter is a subClass from Packet_Fittering_Routers","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Single_Homed_Bastion is a subClass from Packet_Fittering_Routers","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Screened_Host_Firewall is a subClass from Packet_Fittering_Routers","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"BASET is a subClass from Gigabit_Ethernet","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"CD is a subClass from Gigabit_Ethernet","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"BASE5 is a subClass from Gigabit_Ethernet","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"IAX is a subClass from VOIP","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"eMail is a subClass from VOIP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Internet_Society is a subClass from VOIP","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Extreme_Network is a subClass from ExtremeXOS","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"ZyNOS is a subClass from ExtremeXOS","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"VRP is a subClass from ExtremeXOS","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Pure_Honeypots is a subClass from Honeypots","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Rule_Based_Detection is a subClass from Honeypots","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Anomaly_Detection is a subClass from Honeypots","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Variable_Bit_Rate is a subClass from ","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Type_5 is a subClass from ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Type_2 is a subClass from ","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"STS-1 is a subClass from SDH","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Internet_Protocol is a subClass from SDH","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Ethernet is a subClass from SDH","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Extranet is a subClass from Scope","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Protocol is a subClass from Scope","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Security is a subClass from Scope","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Application_Layer is a subClass from IP_Suite","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Topology is a subClass from IP_Suite","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Performance is a subClass from IP_Suite","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Firewall is a subClass from System_Security","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Fabrication is a subClass from System_Security","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Confidentiality is a subClass from System_Security","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Spammer_Programs is a subClass from Malicious_Software","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Passive_Attacks is a subClass from Malicious_Software","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Availablity is a subClass from Malicious_Software","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Class_F is a subClass from Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Bonded_TP is a subClass from Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Twisted_Ribbon_Cable is a subClass from Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Active_Hub is a subClass from Hub","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Modem is a subClass from Hub","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Bridge is a subClass from Hub","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Routing_table is a subClass from Router","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Repeater is a subClass from Router","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Gateway is a subClass from Router","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Socket_Address is a subClass from Transport_Layer","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Network_Interface is a subClass from Transport_Layer","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Internet_Layer is a subClass from Transport_Layer","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"PPTP is a subClass from Virtual_Private_Network","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"PPTP is a subClass from Intrusion_Detection_System","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"PPTP is a subClass from Firewall","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"NCP is a subClass from Session","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"NCP is a subClass from ISO_Standard","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"NCP is a subClass from Application","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Forwarding is a subClass from Network","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Forwarding is a subClass from Data_Link","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Forwarding is a subClass from Presentation","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Permanent is a subClass from Point_to_Point","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Permanent is a subClass from Mesh","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Permanent is a subClass from Hybrid","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Stealth_Virus is a subClass from Virus","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Stealth_Virus is a subClass from Logic_Bomb","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Stealth_Virus is a subClass from Backdoor","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Silicon_Photo_Diode is a subClass from Infrared","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Silicon_Photo_Diode is a subClass from Satellites","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Silicon_Photo_Diode is a subClass from Microwave","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SNMPv1 is a subClass from SNMP","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"SNMPv1 is a subClass from BOOTP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SNMPv1 is a subClass from NTP","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"IAX is a subClass from VOIP","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"IAX is a subClass from eMail","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IAX is a subClass from Internet_Society","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"PHP is a subClass from World_Wide_Web","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"PHP is a subClass from IAB","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"PHP is a subClass from G","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Extreme_Network is a subClass from ExtremeXOS","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Extreme_Network is a subClass from ZyNOS","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Extreme_Network is a subClass from VRP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Cisco_Inc. is a subClass from CISCO_IOS","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Cisco_Inc. is a subClass from JUNOS","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Cisco_Inc. is a subClass from MOS","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SIP is a subClass from User_Datagram_Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"SIP is a subClass from Internet_Protocol_Version_6","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SIP is a subClass from Connectionless_Service","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"MIME is a subClass from SMTP","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"MIME is a subClass from DNS","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"MIME is a subClass from DICT","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IMAP2 is a subClass from IMAP","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"IMAP2 is a subClass from Bit_Torrent","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IMAP2 is a subClass from HTTPS","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SCP is a subClass from SSH","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"SCP is a subClass from FTP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SCP is a subClass from SNMP","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Pure_Honeypots is a subClass from Honeypots","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Pure_Honeypots is a subClass from Rule_Based_Detection","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Pure_Honeypots is a subClass from Anomaly_Detection","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Variable_Bit_Rate is a subClass from ","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Variable_Bit_Rate is a subClass from Type_5","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Variable_Bit_Rate is a subClass from Type_2","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"STS-1 is a subClass from SDH","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"STS-1 is a subClass from Internet_Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"STS-1 is a subClass from Ethernet","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Extranet is a subClass from Scope","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Extranet is a subClass from Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Extranet is a subClass from Security","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Switch is a subClass from Networking_Hardware","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Switch is a subClass from IP_Suite","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Switch is a subClass from Topology","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Congession is a subClass from Performance","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Congession is a subClass from Network_Operating_System","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Congession is a subClass from Scale","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Home_Area_Network is a subClass from Local_Area_Network","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Home_Area_Network is a subClass from Campus_Area_Network","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Home_Area_Network is a subClass from Backbone_Network","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Elliptic_Curve_Cryptography is a subClass from Public_Key_Encryption","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Elliptic_Curve_Cryptography is a subClass from Hash_and_Mac_Algebra","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Elliptic_Curve_Cryptography is a subClass from Digital_Signature","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Block_Cipher is a subClass from Symmetrie_Encryption","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Block_Cipher is a subClass from System_Security","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Block_Cipher is a subClass from Fabrication","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Port_Scanner is a subClass from Passive_Attacks","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Port_Scanner is a subClass from Availablity","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Port_Scanner is a subClass from Active_Attacks","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Loaded_TP is a subClass from Twisted_Pair","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Loaded_TP is a subClass from Optical_Fibre","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Loaded_TP is a subClass from Coaxial_Cable","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Class_F is a subClass from Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Class_F is a subClass from Bonded_TP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Class_F is a subClass from Twisted_Ribbon_Cable","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Active_Hub is a subClass from Hub","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Active_Hub is a subClass from Modem","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Active_Hub is a subClass from Bridge","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Socket_Address is a subClass from Transport_Layer","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Socket_Address is a subClass from Network_Interface","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Socket_Address is a subClass from Internet_Layer","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Novel_Netware is a subClass from Server","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Novel_Netware is a subClass from Router_Operating_System","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Novel_Netware is a subClass from Peer_to_Peer","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Type_1 is a subClass from AAL","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Type_1 is a subClass from Data","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Type_1 is a subClass from Video","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which one of the following response pairs are related ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Application\tuses\tRADIUS","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Network\tuses\tRADIUS","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"ISO_Standard\tuses\tRADIUS","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Data_Link\tuses\tRADIUS","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which one of the following response pairs are related ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Internet_Society\tcommittee\tIAB","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"eMail\tcommittee\tIAB","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"VOIP\tcommittee\tIAB","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RFC\tcommittee\tIAB","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"property"}]